[
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"The shops are a lot ___ than usual.",
			"optionA":"quieter",
			"optionB":"more quiet",
			"optionC":"quietter",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"I feel much ___ since I started exercising.",
			"optionA":"fiter",
			"optionB":"fitter",
			"optionC":"more fit",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"The girl ___ than she seemed in her photo.",
			"optionA":"more pretty",
			"optionB":"most pretty",
			"optionC":"prettier",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"The town on Sunday ___.",
			"optionA":"less crowded",
			"optionB":"least crowded",
			"optionC":"crowdeder",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"I think this sofa is ___ than the other.",
			"optionA":"comfortabler",
			"optionB":"more comfortable",
			"optionC":"most comfortable",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"The Eiffel Tower is ___ site in France.",
			"optionA":"the more popular",
			"optionB":"popularest",
			"optionC":"the most popular",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"She is a ___ Musican than her friend.",
			"optionA":"better",
			"optionB":"gooder",
			"optionC":"best",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"What is ___ river in the world?",
			"optionA":"the longer",
			"optionB":"the longest",
			"optionC":"longer than",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Which gloves are ___ ?",
			"optionA":"the cheap",
			"optionB":"more cheaper",
			"optionC":"cheaper",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"My friend is much ___ than I am",
			"optionA":"taller",
			"optionB":"most tall",
			"optionC":"the tallest",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Who is ___ politician in the Parliment?",
			"optionA":"the badest",
			"optionB":"the worst",
			"optionC":"worse",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"What is ___ painting in this Gallery?",
			"optionA":"the more beautiful",
			"optionB":"the beautifulest",
			"optionC":"the most beautiful",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"My car is ___ than yours.",
			"optionA":"less expensive",
			"optionB":"least expensive",
			"optionC":"expensiver",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"It was ___ thing.",
			"optionA":"the less surprising",
			"optionB":"the least surprising",
			"optionC":"the surprisinger",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"It's not ___  it was yesterday.",
			"optionA":"as hot than",
			"optionB":"as hot so",
			"optionC":"as hot as",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"He wasn't ___ I thought he would be.",
			"optionA":"as tall as",
			"optionB":"as tall like",
			"optionC":"the tall as",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"3) The children were ___ gold.",
			"optionA":"more good than",
			"optionB":"as good as",
			"optionC":"less better than",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"The tickets were twice ___  before.",
			"optionA":"as expensive like",
			"optionB":"more expensiver than",
			"optionC":"as expensive as",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"We climbed ___ up the hill.",
			"optionA":"further",
			"optionB":"farer",
			"optionC":"fartest",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"What is the ___ planet from the sun?",
			"optionA":"farest",
			"optionB":"furthest",
			"optionC":"fariest",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	}
]